I feel like when my people go ham and support me, like they don't be in the comments trolling and being mean.
Like they're going to hit you with intellect.
They're going to like break down like your argument and show you how it's like false.
Like that's my supporters.
When I see other people's supporters, I'm like, just so you know, your supporters are just mean and dumb.
And that is not it, honey.
You don't want them out here representing you.
I don't want nobody ever being out there being mean and dumb in my name.
Do not do it in my honor, baby.
It is not it.
We are noble.
We are classy.
We are loving.
That's what we do.
So we will correct folks.
Now, if they come out they face, you know, do what you got to do.
But don't ever feel like I'm wanting y'all to support me in that way.
No, no, no, no, no.
We up here, you know, we're on a high vibration.
It's not just a they go low, go high.
We just, we in another dimension, baby.
That's where we at.